Guide to the Residential College Seminar Program, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Residential College Seminar Program, Yale University, records
1969-2002
RU 320
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
65
The records consist of courses of study, correspondence, budgets, and proposals documenting courses (seminars) offered through the Yale residential colleges.
Yale University. Residential College Seminar Program
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-A (YRG 13-A), Records of the Yale Council of Masters.
Conditions Governing Access
The contents of the records are restricted. See inventory for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of courses of study, correspondence, budgets, and proposals documenting courses (seminars) offered through the Yale residential colleges.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically by semester.
Student housing; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Universities and colleges -- Curricula; Berkeley College (Yale University); Branford College (Yale University); Calhoun College (Yale University); Davenport College (Yale University); Ezra Stiles College (Yale University); Jonathan Edwards College (Yale University); Morse College (Yale University); Pierson College (Yale University); Saybrook College (Yale University); Silliman College (Yale University); Timothy Dwight College (Yale University); Trumbull College (Yale University); Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Curricula; Yale University -- Student housing
- Residential College Seminar Program records, 1969-1993; Accession 1999-A-091
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2028
  - Residential college seminars, 1969-1970 (bound notebook) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Berkeley: Spiro/Freedman, Reynolds, Cassidy, Weisstub, Oberle, Whitback, Watkins/sullivan, Ratanakul (not all listed names appear in folders) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Branford: Ritro, Berrigan, Schyedulhal, Mills, Sitney, Snow, Rose, Graham (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Calhoun:Woeff, Casey, Melman, Lopez, Sachs, Christ, Frankenthaler, Abueva, Jewis, Eames (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Davenport: Robinson, Bauvise, Stein/Burrows, Weisstub, Horwitz, Arnston, Watkins/Sullivan, MacMullen, Freud/Lustmen (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - T.D.Gagarin, Atrally, Louis, Baker, Swain, Lupecha, Kasinski, Nichols, Smith, Dovidoff, Tbath, Yanaga (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - J.E.Hudson, westphal, Raylance/Scharr, Siggins, Francis, Bayley, Walinety, Apter (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Marse:Guilhamet, Marse, Hill, Hodgy, Marowitz, Mahl, Katz, Gellinek, Buch, Mayhew, Anderson, Duran, Voight (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Saybrook: Leavy, danzig, Hahn, Janaga, Hurgan, Buchetal, Elnicki (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Saybrook: Hahn, Yanaga, Elnicki, Savis, Greenberg, Breenburgh, Miller, Ashmole, Logan (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Silliman: Oberle, Price/Hawley, Kaniston, Lewis, Faulkner, Price, Doves, Schaffer (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Silliman:Hunter, Mili, Erwin, Palmer, Libby, Oberle, McBride, Price, Keniston (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ezra Stiles, Fleishman, Snat, Leyda, Clarkson, Posnick, Garwin, Lidz, Repuaci, Lussan, Weisskoff, MacDonald (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Trumbull: ericson/Rosen, Malamawt, Rastow, Alben, Solmit, Griffiths, Barnett, Walch, Schiff (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Trumbull: Hexter, et al, Kazemadeh, Erikson, Magee, Steal, Savage?, Price, Calden, Prelinger, Hartas, Birnbau (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Unlabled File (contains: Broderick, Danzig, Harvey, Hille, Howard, Leavy, Long, Posnick, Wojcik, Garvin (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Vita and Personnel Profile, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Special committee on teaching in residential colleges, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Procedures and policies (residential colleges) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1969-1970 (budget materials) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Budget - correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Final Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Residential college seminars, 1969-1970 (bound notebook) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Course approvals, 1969-1970 (final approval) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Financial correspondence 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Check requests 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bulletin 1969-1970 - residential college seminars (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Lists 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Council of masters, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Course of study comm. (Residential colleges), 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Instructors (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Appointments (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Residential Colleges misc. correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Enrollments 1969-1970 residential college seminars (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Berkeley college 1969-1970 seminars approved and correspondence (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Branford college, 1969-1970 seminars approved and correspondence (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Financial '71- '72 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Desmond CSS498B (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Fall '71 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Berkeley-- P.P. Forms: Reynolds, Wasserman, Reiss, Sweezy, Moyer (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Branford-- Wolf (Gelbach), Stolwijk, Denitch, Silver, Shiffrin, Cavander (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Branford-- Ahern, Johnson, Greenberg, Holahan, Seidman, Breiner (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Calhoun-- McMullen, Zinsser, Yuston, Coffin, Farb, Ribuffo, Paul (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Calhoun-- Kozinski, Cook, Schicke, Clark, Sacks & Lewis (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Davenport-- Oscanyan, Bernstein, Wasserman, Beacham, Sullivan, Silverman, Kleber, Garrer, Brown, Smith, Burdick (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Jonathan Edwards (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Davenport-- Solnit, Kennedy, Davidson, Fox, Wegener, Stepner (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - T.D.-- Smith (5 fellows of T.D., Adelberg, etc.) Berry, Davie, etc., Arnstein, Repucci (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - J.E.-- Zegans, Frey, Klein, Cannon, Muler, Reed, Yeston (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Pierson-- P.P. Forms: Strong, Thomason, Sorkin, Giurgola, Hollander, Hunter (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Morse-- Alvarez, Stimson, Sabarr, Erlich, Morse, Roemer (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Saybrook-- P.P. Forms: Durk, Devine, Sarris, Politt, Hahn, Fabian (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Silliman-- P.P. Forms: Epstein, Davis, Gans, Joskon, Kramer, Levy, Brieff (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Trumbull-- Garvin,Solnit, Magee, Leiner, Kazemzaden, Rouse (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - (T.D. Proposal-- Wizner) (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Check Requests (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - (T.D., Berkeley, Stiles) (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Berkeley-- P.P. Forms: Frankel, Chen, Parke, David (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Berkeley-- Noakes (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Branford-- Seidman, Stobetad, Cain, Wolfowitz (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Mills-- CSBR- 68a (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Branford-- Cavander, Glazer, Ruff, Silver, Henderson, Crawford, Brown (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Calhoun- Nelson, Cutts, Coreadi, Carden (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Calhoun-- Gutry (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Calhoun-- Semetz, Coffin, Fenn, Winer, Aschette, Lukas (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Davenport-- Richardson, Coffin, Vickery, Skinner (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Personal Profile Forms-- '72- '73 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Keys-- CSBR2A (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Residential College Seminars (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - T.D. -- Frederick (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Morse-- Delgodo, Cohn, Jochnowitz, Hill, Snow, Ron, Roemer (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Pierson-- Malaweitz, Hersey, Sorkin, Insler, Shiprian, Peschel, Nemerson (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Saybrook-- Yates, David, Handshumacher, etc., Richardson, Bunges (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Lewis CSCC4A (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Goodman CSSMIA-CSCC1A (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Silliman-- Wheeler, Kramer, Palmer, Lytle, Riberian, Dann (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Silliman-- Kagen, Yargen, Judson, Rouse (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Ezra Stiles-- Shapiro, Thompson, First, Meisel, Rovere, Stankiewic (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Derek Price (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Giliomee CSBK11A (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Turekian CSBK6A (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Knirk CSBK2A (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Wolf CSBR 92A (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Dotan CSDC CSPS 12A+B (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Pagelson CSCC5A CSBR5A (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Charles Hortas, Manuel Del Valle (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Robert Stockstad BR11b (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Rosemary Bletter BR16 B (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Mark Strand BR12B (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Wanda Bershan (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - R.W.B. Lewis (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Gaster CSCC3A CSTC3A (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Schlamma CSCC6A (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Frank Huband CC27B (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Brenda Stiers (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Kauffman CSCC8A (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Gail Marcus DC25B (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Joy Wulke DC 20B (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Solotorroff (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Charles Nesbit, Elliot Schwartz, Christine Osinski (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Joseph Reed (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Jennifer Wing TD 11B (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Lucille Ritvo TD 15Bb (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Babbidge- CSTD3a (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Timothy dwight college courses/expenses, 1973/1974 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Kennedy- CSTD 76A (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Pollack- CSDC 2a (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Johnson- CSDC4a (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Joseph Lieberman TD14B (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Gary Morson TD 13B (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Wyner- CSTD5a (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Yasin Al-Khalesi TD 16B (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - JE Anderson, Byrd, Hutchinson, Clark, Bunnel, Huhn (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Jonathon Edwards courses/expenses, 1973/1974 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Turk-CSJE23-CSS423 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Wind-CSJE 20A (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Wheeler CSJE 90B (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Thompson CSJE84a+84b (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Sheard CSJEIMC- 1A (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - John Montias CSJE 15B (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - LEC-CSS94A-CSJE4a (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Kuehn- CSJE 14B (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Ritchie/Hitchcock CSJE11A (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Apter CSJE 13B (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Howard - CSMC 2a (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - John Devine MC93B (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Stern CSMC83a Repeat (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Mahl-CSMC-84a-repeat (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Charles Cutter MC23B (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Anthony Lewis PC 23B (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Jean Valentine PC 28B (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Davis CSPC 1A (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Kateb CSPC2a (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Bankwitz CSPC14B (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Joan Panetti CSPC3a (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Shafer CSP76B repeat (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Leavy CSSY 916 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Hortas-del-valle-CSSY12A+TC-12A (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Curron-CSSY4a+CSTC4a (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Carol O'Connor BK/SY 24B (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Richardson CSSY 7a-7b CSBK B1 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Wheeler CSSM11b (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Jonathan Marks SM21b (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Norma Bernstein SM18b (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Kenneth Abraham SM17b (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Anthony Waters SM16b (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Thomson CSSM6A (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - James Shaw SM23b (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Faulkner CSSM2A (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Hirsch CSES-3A (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Eleaonore Frey ES21b (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Moneygal CSES 7A (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Lynn Landmesser CSES1A (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Gordon CSES 2b (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Ezra Stiles: Courses/Expenses (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Reilly CSES6A (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Schwartz CSES83A (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Anthony Kronman TC 27b (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Susanna Barrows TC/DC 24b (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Henry Abelove TC/SY 8b (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Nadel & Crawshaw CSTC 26b (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Ogilvy CSTC85A/ CSSC85A (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Solnit CSTC23A (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Solomon CSTC1A (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Garven CSTC9/ CSCC9 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Thomas Bernstein TC/DC 29b (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Leon Lipson TC28b (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - McDonald CSBR1A (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Phyllis Lafarge TD 40b (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Thomas Clifton MC4a (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Galambas CSS418A (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Robert Byer ES/ SM34A (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Kenneth Rogoff SM33A (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Ellen Geffner Joyce TC45A (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Smith CSPC 22A (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Vanwelly & Remington CSPC2A (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Philip Grausman CSS9 25A CSJEA (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Otto & Claus SY28a (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Robert Entman CC/SY 36a (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - George McCully (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Andrea Bertolini ES 23a (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Mark Rose DC Fall 1974 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - John Kennedy Fall 1974 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Lorraine Burbar Fall 1974 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Wainwright CSBK 4b (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Kleber/Tucker CSDC 61A (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Weisbrod CSTD1A (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Carolyn Heilburn (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Davis 4acoe-cc/ JE 33a (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Michael Avery (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Betty Freiden (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - John Kao TC/DC 38a (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - David Papke (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Kleber and Mandel DC 34A (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Frank Richards DC/ BK 27b (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - f. Richards DC 27b (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - J. Palmer SM 39b (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Oppenheimer: SillimanWorkshop (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Robert Shrum SM 41b (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Ezra Stiles: Courses/Expenses (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - R. Lewis ES40b (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Brigitte Peuker ES 37b (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - R. Copeland ES44b (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Devitch/Vlock: Ezra Stiles workshop (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - James Simon ES12b (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Valery Chalidze ES38b (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Trumbull College-- Courses/ Expenses (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Robert C. Gogosian TC 41b (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - P Vinter-Johansen TC43b/ BK43b (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Charles Sommerfield TC31a (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Bellis-- Trumbull Workshop (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Timothy Dwight: Courses and Expenses (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Peter Judd (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Walter Rosenblum TD 43b (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Granger CSTD2a (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Chen-- TD workshop (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - S. Marshall Cohen TD 41b (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Brandy CSJE 21A (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Jonathan Edwards: Courses and Expenses (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Michael Waitzken JE 35b (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Robert Haynes JE 36b (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Steven Rosenthal JE 16b (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - M. Resnick JE 44b/ DC 44b (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Resnick CSJE12A (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - (Blue Book) Residential College Seminars (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Leonard Zegans JE22A (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - L.C. Austin JE 83b (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Milstein, Babbidge, Davie (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - S. Felman JE 38b (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - Morse College: Courses and Expenses (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Logan MC 25A (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - S. Dovydov MC 31b (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - J.Robertson MC32b (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - Morse CSMC 3b (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Richard Shiels, MC21b (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - Hwang-- Morse Workshop (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Pierson College-- Courses and Expences (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - John Iatrides PC 41b/BK 41b (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - Emmy Devine PC 43b (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - D. Cast PC46b/ CC46b (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Gavin Hambly PC 32A (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - A. David PC 48b/ SY48 b (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - Saybrook Colleges: Courses and Expenses (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Delaney Kiputh SY 42b/ TD 42b (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Handschmacher, Miller & Co.-- CSSY Za+b (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Joel Rogers SY 47b/ ES 47b (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - R. Reeder SY 46b/ BK 45b (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - Silliman College: Courses and Expenses (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - S. Lawder SM 45b/ CC45b (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Freccero & Rosanova SM 49b/ CC49b (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - James Bardeen SM 30a/ ES 30a/ CC30a (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - Jethro Lieberman SM 43b/ DC 43b (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - S. Rosenthal CC41b/ BR41b (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - Yannis Simonides CC43b/ BR43b (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - H. Coffin CC48b/ SM 48b (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - Louis Font CECC50bCSSY50b (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - Keurten: Calhoun workshop repeat (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - S. Rockmore DC41b (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - J. Vivian DC 42b (Box 6, Folder 267)
  - Skinner & Thomson DC39b (Box 6, Folder 268)
  - Leavitt: Davenport Workshop (Box 6, Folder 269)
  - Hirsch: Davenport Workshop (Box 6, Folder 270)
  - Fall 1973 Brown CSCC (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Fall 1973 Cochran CSSM4a (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Fall 1973 Hundt CSDC11A (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Fall 1973 Tedlow CSCC 7a (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Fall 1973 Maxwell CSCC CSBR (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Fall 1973 Nesbitt CSTD (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Fall 1972 Whitbeck CSBR (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - Fall 1973 Kosinsk CSTD (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Fall 1973 McIntosh (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Fall 1973 Cooke- withdrawn (Box 7, Folder 280)
  - Fall 1973 Gascon-Vera CSSY-CSTC (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - Fall 1973 Foster CSES (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Fall 1973 Sametz CSCC-CSBR (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - Fall 1973 Madeleine Trinkaus BR (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - Fall 1973 Tannenbaum (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Fall 1973 Lobdell-CSBR (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - Fall 1973 David Shwartz BR (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - Spring 1974 Carapetyan (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Spring 1974 David Stannard (Box 7, Folder 289)
  - Spring 1974 Tuck CSSM (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - Spring =74 Mills CSES (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Spring 1974 Don Yacoe (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - Peter Davis CC34b/ PC34b (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - J. Parr CC45b/ ES45b (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Goodman CSCC1A (Box 7, Folder 295)
  - M. Everett BR 44b/ C44b (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - Eric Broudy (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - Sarah Pauly (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - Irving Zaretsky BR 42b (Box 7, Folder 299)
  - Peter Clegg BK/BR 37A (Box 7, Folder 300)
  - J. Logue SM518 (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - David Warren TC 39b/PC 39b (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - D. Dobkin BR 39b (Box 8, Folder 304)
  - James Carse BR 40b (Box 8, Folder 305)
  - Smith & Reifsynder BK40b/JE40b (Box 8, Folder 306)
  - Arnold W. Frutkin BK42b (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - Sidney E. Rolfe CSBK 44b (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Spring 1975 Neill CSDC (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Spring 1975 Douglas Yates (Box 8, Folder 310)
  - Spring 1975 Peter Neill SY 41b (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - Spring 1975 Stephen Glickman MC22b (Box 8, Folder 312)
  - Spring 1975 Johnson CSSY (Box 8, Folder 313)
  - Fall 1975 Veto CSMC36A (Box 8, Folder 314)
  - Spring 1975 Mortimer CSJE (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - Spring 1975 McCully CSDC 40b (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Spring 1975 White CSMC (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - Fall 1975 Veto CSPC 56A (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - Elizabeth Henderson ES/TD 33A (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - Fall 1975 Nayak CSDC (Box 8, Folder 320)
  - Fall 1975 Schopero CSSY (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - (Fall 1975 Henderson CS) (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Ziegler TD49A REPEAT (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Comisso TD 48A (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Van Wegenen JE/BR 46A (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - (no manilla folder) (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Brown JE47A (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Bettelheim TD46A (Box 8, Folder 329)
  - Margaret Mahar MC29A (Box 8, Folder 330)
  - Kaczynski MC36A (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - Stewart MC 37A (Box 8, Folder 332)
  - McNulty PC/BK 55A (Box 8, Folder 333)
  - Rethis SY52A (Box 8, Folder 334)
  - 1975-76 committee on teaching in the residential colleges (no manilla folder) (Box 8, Folder 335)
  - Poverman SY53A Repeat (Box 8, Folder 336)
  - Mitgang SM/ CC 55A (Box 8, Folder 337)
  - Godzich SM 53A (Box 8, Folder 338)
  - Hill & Meredith ES 52A REPEAT (Box 8, Folder 339)
  - Garey TC46A (Box 8, Folder 340)
  - Hudson TC 49A (Box 8, Folder 341)
  - Welleck TC47A (Box 8, Folder 342)
  - Henry Turner BK 28A (Box 8, Folder 343)
  - Perlis BR 50A (Box 8, Folder 344)
  - Tallmadge JE 41A (Box 8, Folder 345)
  - Reynolds CSBK 4A+b (Box 8, Folder 346)
  - (Gould) (Box 8, Folder 347)
  - Paul Holmer BR 57A, DC57A (Box 8, Folder 348)
  - Gilson CC60A (Box 8, Folder 349)
  - Mauldin CC/ SM 63A REPEAT (Box 8, Folder 350)
  - Figueroa CC/ SY 70A (Box 8, Folder 351)
  - Hollingsworth CC/ SM 58A (Box 8, Folder 352)
  - Sawyer BR 49A (Box 8, Folder 353)
  - Reily BK/ SM 56A REPEAT (Box 9, Folder 354)
  - Zelitch DC/ BK 60A (Box 9, Folder 355)
  - Mitford, CSCC71b/ CSSC71b (Box 9, Folder 356)
  - Schuettinger DC33A REPEAT (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Dutton DC45A REPEAT (Box 9, Folder 358)
  - Merrill DC/CC 61A (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - Kazlovsky CC/SM 59A (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - Gwirtzman CC/ TC 62A (Box 9, Folder 361)
  - Powers DC/ BK 59A REPEAT (Box 9, Folder 362)
  - Marx CSDC/ CSES 48A REPEAT (Box 9, Folder 363)
  - Silberman CSTC CSPC (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Tannebaum CSTD Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Jenkins CSSY Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 366)
  - Lansing CSDC Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 367)
  - Rush CSPC/ CSBR 65b (Box 9, Folder 368)
  - Rush JE 42A (Box 9, Folder 369)
  - Evaluation of Special Committee (1970-=71) (Box 9, Folder 370)
  - Timothy Dwight Budget and Costs Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 371)
  - Frey CSTD 56b (Box 9, Folder 372)
  - Logue CSTD 55b (Box 9, Folder 373)
  - Satter CSTD 54b (Box 9, Folder 374)
  - Laughlin CSTD 57b (Box 9, Folder 375)
  - Davie and Milstein TD 51A+b (Box 9, Folder 376)
  - J.E. Budget and Costs Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 377)
  - Kosodoy CSJE 56b (Box 9, Folder 378)
  - Kelley CSJE/ CSBK 5A (Box 9, Folder 379)
  - Cooper CSJE 49b (Box 9, Folder 380)
  - Klein CSJE/ CSMC 55b (Box 9, Folder 381)
  - Pogorelskin CSJE 57b (Box 9, Folder 382)
  - Kelley CSJE 51b (Box 9, Folder 383)
  - Morse College Budgets and Costs, Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 384)
  - Jubin, CSMC 51b (Box 9, Folder 385)
  - Boly, CSMC 53b (Box 9, Folder 386)
  - Thelwell, CSMC 39b (Box 9, Folder 387)
  - Schickel, CSPC 73b (Box 9, Folder 388)
  - Sullivan PC 83b (Box 9, Folder 389)
  - Pierson Budgets and Costs Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 390)
  - Laurence CSPC/ CSES 67b (Box 9, Folder 391)
  - Prusoff CSPC/ CSBK 66b (Box 9, Folder 392)
  - Pessl, CSPC 71b (Box 9, Folder 393)
  - Megehan, CSPC/ CSTC 76b (Box 9, Folder 394)
  - Heaps CSPC/ CSTC 69b (Box 9, Folder 395)
  - Hersey, CSTC 67b/ CSPC 70b (Box 9, Folder 396)
  - Hersey, CSPC 40b (Box 9, Folder 397)
  - Saybrook Budget and Costs Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 398)
  - Rethis, CSSY64b (Box 9, Folder 399)
  - McFeeley, CSSY62b/ CSBK62b (Box 9, Folder 400)
  - Jordon, CSBK 63b (Box 9, Folder 401)
  - Greene, CSBK 65b (Box 9, Folder 402)
  - Sherry, CSBR 53b/ CSTD 53b (Box 9, Folder 403)
  - Sawyer, CSBR 49b (Box 9, Folder 404)
  - Bair, CSBR 54b (Box 9, Folder 405)
  - Bettelheim, CSBR 55b (Box 9, Folder 406)
  - Sylvia Fine Kaye CC47b/ TD47b (Box 9, Folder 407)
  - Calhoun, Spring 1976 (Box 9, Folder 408)
  - Kabayashi, CSCC 76b/ CSSY76b/ CSSM76b (Box 9, Folder 409)
  - Engel, CSCC 74b (Box 9, Folder 410)
  - Yeager, CSCC 72b (Box 9, Folder 411)
  - Dahl, CSCC 73b/ CSBK73b (Box 9, Folder 412)
  - R. Dahl CC40b/SM40b (Box 9, Folder 413)
  - Dickerman CSCC 78b (Box 9, Folder 414)
  - Thorpe, CSCC75b/ CSTC 75b (Box 9, Folder 415)
  - Brandon, CSDC 65b (Box 10, Folder 416)
  - Norberg, CSDC 69b/ CSSM 69b (Box 10, Folder 417)
  - Mancusi-Ungaro CSDC 62b (Box 10, Folder 418)
  - Brandstein CSBK94b/ CSPC94b (Box 10, Folder 419)
  - Brandstein JE81A (Box 10, Folder 420)
  - Brandstein CSSM 68b/ CSJE 68b (Box 10, Folder 421)
  - Sinclair 1976-=77 CSBK98b/ CSJE98b (Box 10, Folder 422)
  - Barney BK 75A (Box 10, Folder 423)
  - Reifman BK84A (Box 10, Folder 424)
  - Alfred Reifman BK83b (Box 10, Folder 425)
  - Paris et al BK 67A (Box 10, Folder 426)
  - Spiro and Paris BK38b (Box 10, Folder 427)
  - LoebCSBK 96b (Box 10, Folder 428)
  - Aptheker DC63A (Box 10, Folder 429)
  - Aptheker DC63A (Box 10, Folder 430)
  - Shweizer JE82A Fall 1976 (Box 10, Folder 431)
  - Nussdorfer CSDC 71A Fall 1976 (Box 10, Folder 432)
  - Auletta CSDC 70A Fall 1976 (Box 10, Folder 433)
  - Silberman TC 72A Fall 1976 (Box 10, Folder 434)
  - Kodama BR66A (Box 10, Folder 435)